export const Quastions ={
    math:{

        vize:[
            {
                prompt :"vize?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"21",
                optionC:"4",
                optionD:"2",
                answer :"C",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 5+5?",
                optionA: "11",
                optionB:"12",
                optionC:"1",
                optionD:"10",
                answer :"D",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 6+3?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"9",
                optionC:"8",
                optionD:"13",
                answer :"B",
            },
        ],
        final:[
            {
                prompt :"final?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"21",
                optionC:"4",
                optionD:"2",
                answer :"C",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 5+5?",
                optionA: "11",
                optionB:"12",
                optionC:"1",
                optionD:"10",
                answer :"D",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 6+3?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"9",
                optionC:"8",
                optionD:"13",
                answer :"B",
            },
        ]

        
    },

    fizik:{

        vize:[
            {
                prompt :"vize?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"21",
                optionC:"4",
                optionD:"2",
                answer :"C",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 5+5?",
                optionA: "11",
                optionB:"12",
                optionC:"1",
                optionD:"10",
                answer :"D",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 6+3?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"9",
                optionC:"8",
                optionD:"13",
                answer :"B",
            },
        ],
        final:[
            {
                prompt :"final?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"21",
                optionC:"4",
                optionD:"2",
                answer :"C",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 5+5?",
                optionA: "11",
                optionB:"12",
                optionC:"1",
                optionD:"10",
                answer :"D",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 6+3?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"9",
                optionC:"8",
                optionD:"13",
                answer :"B",
            },
        ]

        
    },
    bio:{

        vize:[
            {
                prompt :"vize?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"21",
                optionC:"4",
                optionD:"2",
                answer :"C",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 5+5?",
                optionA: "11",
                optionB:"12",
                optionC:"1",
                optionD:"10",
                answer :"D",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 6+3?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"9",
                optionC:"8",
                optionD:"13",
                answer :"B",
            },
        ],
        final:[
            {
                prompt :"final?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"21",
                optionC:"4",
                optionD:"2",
                answer :"C",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 5+5?",
                optionA: "11",
                optionB:"12",
                optionC:"1",
                optionD:"10",
                answer :"D",
            },
            {
                prompt :"What is 6+3?",
                optionA: "24",
                optionB:"9",
                optionC:"8",
                optionD:"13",
                answer :"B",
            },
        ]

        
    },
  
};

